# JONATHAN ROSS

123 Main Street, Austin, TX 12345 j-ross@youremail.com (012) 345-6789 Highly skilled and dependable mechanic with eight years of hands-on experience. Extensive knowledge of the workings of a wide range of gasoline and diesel vehicles. Well-versed in understanding technical documentation and familiar with a variety of components. Able to explain service schedules and mechanical issues to clients.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### LEAD MECHANIC

General Motors West Side, Austin R | November 2016-Present

- Supervise a team of five mechanics and three apprentices
- Diagnose, troubleshoot and repair problems on a wide range of vehicles
- Manage the day-to-day schedule of repair projects and vehicles coming in for scheduled services
- Test drive vehicles to ensure all issues have been resolved
- · Leading the workshop to receive two national awards for high-quality workmanship and excellent customer service

#### **MECHANIC**

Quality Motors, Austin, TX I July 2012 - October 2016

- Worked under the direction and supervision of a Master Mechanic
- Performed routine scheduled services on a variety of vehicles
- ♦ Spoke to an average of 57 customers each week and discussed Labor, repair, and service schedules
- ♦ Finished all jobs 13% faster than the company average

#### **EDUCATION**

# ASSOCIATES DEGREE IN AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING

Austin Cummunity Col Lege At st r () September 2010 - June 2012

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Troubleshooting
- Leadership
- Maintenance procedures
- Inspecting vehicles
- · Rebuilding engines

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

ASF A-Series Certification, Master Auto
Technician, National Institute of Automotive
Service Excellence, 2018